你看了这个吗? 瞧瞧
Are you watching this? Look at this.
关于人质 肖恩·潘做得都比我们多 (著名硬汉影星)
Sean Penn is doing more about the hostages than we are.
这些可怜的孩子...他们和Caterine差不多大
These poor kids... they're like Catherine's age.
我在人质危机中表现肯定会很糟 就算当劫匪也不会好
I'd be terrible in a hostage situation, even as a hostage taker.
女士 国防部长那还没有任何
So, ma'am, no word yet from the Secretary of Defense
关于和他一起去海军基地的答复吗
about joining him at the Marine base?
唔 没有 Maddox什么都没说
Uh, no, nothing from Maddox,
但他知道我现在在白宫的影响更大了
but he knows I've got a bigger role in the White House now,
也就是说我有个更大的屌让他吸了
which means I've got a bigger dick, which means he can suck it.
那真令人高兴 我的演讲怎么样了?
I'm so happy about that. How's my speech coming?
哦 就一个小改动 就一个词 真的
Oh, one minor change. Just one word, really.
经过深思熟虑的答复将变成坚定的答复
Considered response is now gonna be robust response.
坚定的? 见鬼 这真不错
Robust? Damn, that's good.
嗯 我是说 它微妙得足够让我们向总统示忠
Yeah, I mean, it's subtle enough to seem loyal to POTUS.
那会让特区激动得过电的 哦 那会给特区通上交流电
- That's gonna electrify DC. - Oh, it's gonna AC DC.
坚定是个好词
Robust is a good word.
而且你不常听到 就像自以为是一样
And you don't hear it often, like bumptious.
是的 它就是你想在人质危机时听到的
Yeah, it's what you want to hear in a hostage crisis.
坚定 不是自以为是
Robust, not bumptious.
Mike 你觉得怎么样? 坚定这个词怎么样?
Mike, what do you think? What do you think about robust?
坚定? 我喜欢 让我想到了酒 (robust也表示香味浓烈)
Robust? I like it. It makes me think of wine.
事实上我喜欢那样的红酒
It's actually how I like my reds.
你还喜欢用弯曲的吸管喝红酒 对吗 Mike
You like your reds through a bendy straw, too, right, Mike?
Mike 你身上有甜甜圈
You got donut on you, Mike.
Sue 祝你在听证会一切顺利
Sue, good luck at the hearing.
记住 Sue 要装傻 我会的
- Remember, Sue, be dull. - I will.
你是来开会的吗?我没约任何人
Are you here for a meeting? I'm not expecting anyone.
Sue 我是临时来顶你班的 Cliff Cliff 嘿 我是Gary
- Sue, I'm your fill-in, Cliff. - Cliff. Hey, I'm Gary.
我是你的邻居 记住 照顾好Selina 好吗?
I'm your neighbor. Remember, take care of Selina, okay?
VP代表很珍贵
VP stands for very precious.
懂吗? 是的
Okay? - Okay.
Cliff 在
Cliff. - Yes.
这是副总统百科全书
This is the Veeplopedia.
里面有一切你需要知道的东西
It's everything you'll ever need to know.
喔 希望这个有随赠读书笔记 (类似教材参考书的东西)
Wow. Hope it comes with CliffsNotes.
那是个和我名字有关的文字游戏 我的名字是Cliff
That was a play on my name. My name is Cliff.
别开玩笑 Cliff
Don't do jokes, Cliff.
我没有幽默感而你也不该有
I don't have a sense of humor and neither should you.
早上好
Good morning.
你怎么能把两个令人愉悦的词变得如此讨厌呢?
How do you make two perfectly pleasant words so irritating?
就是他 那个不给他的蛋做民调就
And here he is, the man who can't take a leak
尿不出来的男人
without polling his balls.
把我的樱桃色活页文件夹拿来 Jonah
Bring me my cerise-colored binder, Jonah.
樱桃色?是的 先生
Cerise? Yes, sir.
副总统的基地访问就是今天
The VP's base visit today.
国防部长Maddox没有辜负他的名字
Secretary of Defense Maddox is living up to his name.
他气得跟公牛一样发狂
He's mad as an ox.
我很确定只要我一到那就能阻止任何激烈的争辩
I'm sure I can break up any catfights when I get there.
副总统更关注人质的情况
The veep's more concerned with the hostage situation.
是的 我昨晚和总统谈过了
Yeah, I was talking to POTUS last night.
他都同意得那话儿站起来有Jonah那么高了
He had a pro-strike hawk boner the size of Jonah.
而你今天早上和他谈话后
And then you talked to him about it this morning
他突然就很反对这项行动了
and he's suddenly totally against the operation.
我只是把民调结果给了总统而已
All I do is provide POTUS with the polls.
冰冷的数字 上帝 我恨数字
- Cold numbers. - God, I hate numbers.
很多文化甚至都没有数字 但他们过得很好
There's cultures that don't even have any numbers and they do just fine.
好吧 Ben 看上去你并不适合现在的工作 你该辞职
Well, Ben, it seems like you're ill-suited for your job and you should resign.
把Ben的衰弱放一边 副总统觉得
Ben's breakdown aside, the VP feels we need
我们需要一次迅速的军事袭击
a quick military strike here.
是的 严格又精确 就像你的前脑叶白质切除术一样 Kent
Yeah, precise and surgical, like your lobotomy, Kent.
樱桃色活页夹 先生 不 这是桃红色
- The cerise binders, sir. - No, that's cherry red.
樱桃色 抱歉 先生
- Cerise. - I'm sorry, sir.
我肯定有某种特殊的色盲
I must have a very specific form of color blindness.
我每天都做这种面
I cook these noodles every day.
哦 面的比喻
Oh, the noodle analogy.
你们会喜欢的
You guys are gonna love this.
我马上离开
I will leave.
它们得在800瓦的功率下加热
They need to be heated at 800 watts
3分35秒
for three minutes and 35 seconds.
超过就会太干
Any more and they'll dry out.
时间少了它们就会软趴趴湿哒哒的
Any less and they will be flaccid and damp
就像雨天里女人的头发一样
like a lady's hair in the rain.
我们为什么要谈论面条? 不 让我换个问法
- Why are we talking about noodles? - No, let me rephrase that.
我们他妈为什么要讨论面条?
Why the fuck are we talking about noodles?
我会告诉你原因 人质危机 面条...一样的原则
I'll tell you why. Hostage crisis, noodles... same principle.
全都要求精确的时机把握 都不能匆忙处理
Both require precision timing, neither should be rushed.
只有在65%以上的美国人支持不计伤亡
Inaction only becomes untenable when more than 65% of Americans
采取干预措施的时候行动时机才成熟
support intervention even with casualties.
所以你想让我告诉副总统在那之前我们什么都不干?
So you'd like me to tell the vice president we do nothing until then?
等待不是什么都不做
Waiting is not doing nothing.
我选择等我的面条
I choose to wait for my noodles
就算我的唾液腺朝我大喊
even though my salivary glands are crying out to me
像新生的幼鸟一样
like newly hatched birds.
但它们会感谢我 因为我会一直等到...
But they will thank me because I waited until...
你就为了等你这一叮
You just timed out that whole shit analogy
把刚才的时间用狗屎比喻给糊过去了?
for your little ding?
真你妈可悲
That is fucking pathetic.
嘿 Maddox那有任何消息吗
Hey, have we heard anything from Maddox?
他有因为我在基地出现而吐子弹么?
Is he spitting bullets 'cause I'm showing up at the base?
什么也没有 真的吗
Nothing. Nada. - Really?
那挺可怕 不是吗 是挺可怕
- It's eerie, right? - It is eerie.
嘿 Neilio 我们进来了
Hey, Neilio. We're in.
到里面见 我猜
See you in there, I guess.
好的 谢谢
Okay. Thanks.
他的头大概塞进屁股里了
Probably got his head stuck in her ass.
是的 我有 哦 天哪 是的
Yes, I do. Oh, my gosh, yes.
嘿 女士 在Maddox到之前你有五分钟副总统的时间
Hey, ma'am, you've got five minutes of veep time before Maddox arrives.
是的 他们没有对你行礼
- Yeah. - They're not saluting you.
他们在室内不行礼 Gary
They don't salute indoors, Gary.
早上好 陆战队员们 女士
- Good morning, Marine. - Ma'am.
你在伊拉克服役过?我知道了
You served in Iraq? I see.
那么你有到...附近
And were you anywhere near...
巴格达 安巴尔
Baghdad. - Anbar.
...安巴尔? 是的
- ...Anbar? - Yes.
安巴尔 太棒了
Anbar, wonderful.
女士 这个基地驻扎的是陆战二队
Ma'am, this base houses Marine 2.
我知道陆战二队在这里
I understand that Marine 2 is here.
你知道我CD播放器里有《飞行的女武神》吗 (瓦格纳著名进行曲)
And did you know in the CD player I've got Ride of the Valkyries?
《现代启示录》
Apocalypse Now.
是我最喜欢的电影之一 黑暗 但我喜欢
That's one of my favorite films. It's dark, but I like it.
陆战队员们喜欢被称作魔犬 魔犬
Marines Like to be called Devil Dogs. - Devil Dogs.
你们就是一群魔犬 这就是我听说的
You are a bunch of Devil Dogs, that's what I hear.
我嫁给了一只魔犬 但他不是海军陆战队的
I was married to a Devil Dog, but he wasn't a Marine.
他比魔鬼更黑暗
He was more of a devil.
她真有趣
She's so funny.
谢谢你对国家的贡献
Thank you for your service.
早上好  陆战队员 他有张漂亮的脸
- Good morning, Marine. - He has a nice face.
你有张漂亮的脸 谢谢 女士
- You have a nice face. - Thank you, ma'am.
你在哪服役来着 陆战队员?
And where did you serve, Marine?
停止开火!停止开火!
Cease fire! Cease fire!
这些小型武器的有效射程是25码
These small arms have a max effective range of 25 yards.
小型武器指的是手枪 女士
Small arms means guns, ma'am.
哦 是吗 Gary?不是霸王龙的手? (小短手) 好吧
- Oh, really, Gary? Not T-rex hands? - Okay.
部长先生 您要试试么
Mr. Secretary, would you like to try?
不 我很好 我开过枪
No, I'm good. I've fired a gun before.
好吧
Okay.
在盛怒之下 我恐怕得加上 哦 喔哦
- In anger, too, I might add. - Oh, uh-oh.
不过你为什么不试试 副总统女士?
But why don't you give it a try, Madam Vice President?
哦 我不
Oh, I don't...
唔 你能给我半秒钟么
Um, can you give me just half a sec?
搞毛啊
What the fuck?
可能会回火 不可能会回火
- This could backfire. - It's not gonna backfire.
正确的说 手枪是会回火的 那个词就是这么来的
The gun could literally backfire. That's where the phrase comes from.
女士 这也会击败Maddox
Ma'am, this could really chap Maddox's ass, too.
哦 是的 那会 会吗?
Oh, yeah, it would, wouldn't it?
你的牙齿贴片可能会崩的 我真心不希望发生那样的事
You could chip a veneer and I don't really want that to happen.
我不管了 我去了
I don't care. I'm going in.
你们知道吗? 拉上保险然后装子弹 怎么样?
You know what? Let's lock and load. What do you say?
是吗? 是
Yeah? Yeah.
就是他 西翼Kanye
Here he is, Kanye West Wing.
国会议员Ramsey 对吗?
Congressman Ramsey, right?
不 我是Cliff 我是Sue的Sue
No, I'm Cliff. I'm Sue's Sue.
我是那个叫Sue的男孩 什么?
- I'm the boy named Sue. - What?
Cliff 我说不开玩笑 那就不是个玩笑
Cliff, when I said no jokes, that wasn't a joke.
Sue Hessler的效率听证会 你得装傻 懂吗
Sue, Hessler's efficiency hearing, you've got to keep it dull, okay?
就给他们说废话
Give 'em a blah job. Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
我知道 Jonah 每个人都这么说
I know, Jonah. That's what everyone's been saying.
装傻这个行为本身就很傻
Keep it dull, which incidentally, is also dull.
首先我想感谢副总统
I'd like to first of all thank the vice president
舍弃了行政特权
for waiving executive privilege
为了透明度
in the interest of transparency
并允许Wilson小姐今天出席
and allowing Miss Wilson to join us today on the committee.
你觉得她紧张吗?
Do you think she's nervous?
她为什么要紧张?
Why would she be nervous?
会看这个的除了你就只有
The only people watching this are you
医院里那群有闭锁综合征的人了 (无法动弹)
and some guy in the hospital with locked-in syndrome.
如果可以 我想从
If I may, I'd like to begin with percentages
你们办公室划分给国际国内运输
of your office budget dedicated to international
的那部分预算开始 我的脉搏都狂跳了 先生
- and domestic transportation. - My pulse is racing, sir.
给 副总统女士
Here you are, Madam Vice President.
请确保你的手指是直的 并且不在扳机上
Ensure you keep your finger straight and off the trigger.
好 这很有意思 不是吗?
All right. This is fun, isn't it?
如果你不介意我说 女士 那是平民的语气
If you don't mind my saying, ma'am, there speaketh a civilian.
好吧 那是蠢货的语气
All right. There speaketh a pricketh.
哦 我勒个大艹
Oh, Jesus fucking Christ!
Oh!
哦 我很抱歉 我无意...
Oh, I'm so sorry. I didn't...
这些伙计们听过比那更糟糕的 女士
These fellas have heard a lot worse than that, ma'am.
顺说 惊人的射击 真的?
- Tremendous shot, by the way. - Really?
哦 那个怎么样?西翼最快的枪
Oh, how about that? Fastest gun in the West Wing.
你看到了吗? 是的 女士
- - Did you see that? How about it? Yes, ma'am.
就像你们知道的 今天我们这有个很特殊的客人
As you know, we have a very special guest here today.
如果之前能讨论你的演讲就好了 女士
It would have been nice to have been consulted about your speech, ma'am.
我可以给你一些建议
I could have given you some advice.
我知道我在做什么 George
I know what I'm doing, George.
对于人质危机
With this hostage situation,
我不认为你有足够的情报(智力)来处理
I don't think you have the intelligence.
我当然说的是情报 女士
As in intel, of course, ma'am.
你认真的?
Are you serious?
你现在是在质疑我的资格 George?
Are you actually questioning my qualifications, George?
那只是些有关
There are just some security issues
乌兹别克斯坦周围四个国家的安全问题
with the four countries that neighbor Uzbekistan.
是四个还是五个?
Is it four or is it five?
或者六个? 七个?
Or is it six? Or is it seven?
你不知道 对吗?
You don't know, do you?
是五个
It's five.
那么首先 请欢迎国防部长George Maddox
So first, please welcome the Secretary of Defense George Maddox.
我完全没有准备那个问题
I pulled that straight out of my ass.
你就是为那一刻而生的
You were born for that moment.
我知道 他就是硫磺岛 (硫磺岛战役胜利后美军在该岛折钵山上插入国旗)
I know. He's Iwo Jima.
我正在他的头上插旗子
I'm planting a flag right on his head.
如果我们可以 现在我打算将
Now I'd like to work on breaking down
副总统公务上的
the vice president's official
以及政治上的职责分类
versus political duties if we can.
先生 我被告知我会被问及效率方面的问题
Sir, I was told that I'd be asked questions about efficiency.
目前为止你几乎没问过
So far you have barely asked me any.
你的效率听证会可不怎么有效率
Your efficiency hearing isn't very efficient.
你想要问题么?
You want a question? What can you tell me
关于Quantico海军基地的访问你能说些什么?
about this visit to the Marine base at Quantico?
政府让两个不同的车队去同一个地方
The government sending two different motorcades, the defense secretary's
一个是国防部长的 一个是副总统的
and the VP's, to the same location.
那看上去一点效率都没有 哦 他妈的狗屎
- That doesn't seem very efficient. - Oh, shit a shark.
这就是为什么我告诉她要装聋作哑
This is why I told her to be dull.
你们之前难道没有任何
Do you not have measures in place to prevent
可防止此类浪费政府资源的重复行为吗
this kind of wasteful duplication of government resources?
先生 我们有一套我认为很...
Sir, we have a system that I believe to be...
坚定的系统
robust.
坚定? 坚定
Robust? - Robust.
你不觉得那是
And you don't think it's a sign
你们办公室管理松散的信号?
that your office is poorly managed?
我们的管理团队是...坚定的
Our management team is... robust.
好吧 她现在听起来就像精神有问题
Okay, now she just sounds mentally ill.
你就没有你该去的地方?
Don't you have somewhere you're supposed to be?
我正远程工作
I'm working remotely.
我猜你有一份每日一词的日历
I'm guessing you have one of those word a day calendars.
我知道今天的词是什么
And I know what the word for today is.
坚定
It's robust.
你要不要再给我个定义?
Would you like to give me a definition as well?
好吧 我想您认为您有幽默感 Hessler先生
Well, I'm guessing that you think you have a sense of humor, Mr. Hessler.
但您错了 就像您对日历的事情也弄错了一样
Which you are wrong about, as you are about the calendar.
你错误的地方就是我关于坚定的定义
That is my definition of robust.
我的演讲词写得太有冲击力了 这些当兵的肯定都被震了
My speech is a face-melter. These buzz cuts are gonna flip.
那不是你写的演讲词 上面布满了我的指印
It's not your speech. My fingerprints are all over that sucker.
那些指印都很黏糊 而且都在后面 Mike
They're sticky and they're on the back, Mike.
是时候祭出坚定大词镇住全场了
It's time to robust a nut all over this place.
哦 狗屎 我们不能 什么?
- Oh, shit. We can't. - What?
Sue 她在听证会上刚用了三次坚定
Sue, she just used robust three times at the hearing.
不 她没有 是 他妈...
- No, she didn't. - Yeah. What the...?
Selina现在不能用那个 我们需要另一个词
Selina can't use that now. We need another word.
一个坚定的同义词
Just a synonym for robust.
给我什么 给我个词 随便什么词!
Give me something. Give me a word. Any word!
激进的
Aggressive.
不 那太激进了 我们不想说那个
No, that's too aggressive. We don't want to say that.
好吧 坚决的 果断的
- Okay, resolute. - Determined.
那和坚决的是一个意思 那用我的
- That's the exact same thing as resolute. - Then we'll use mine.
爆炸性的 强有力的 无惧的 我只是在随口说而已
Explosive. Punchy. Fearless. I'm just saying words.
强烈的 用强烈的 强烈? 强烈 知道了
- Strong. Go with strong. - Strong? Strong, got it.
Gary 我需要那份演讲 我要副总统的耳朵(附过来)
Gary, I need the speech. I need the vice president's ear.
去找你自己的耳朵吧 梵高
Get your own ear, van Gogh.
退后
Back off.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢 搞什么鬼?
- Thank you. - What the hell?
早上好 陆战队员们
Good morning, Marines!
- Oorah. - Oorah!
哦 天哪
Oh, my goodness.
我们这些选择了
We who have answered the call to serve
为这个伟大国家效力的人都知道
this great nation know this,
那些向我们的自由发起挑战的人
that those who challenge our freedoms
必将得到一个坚定的回答
can expect a robust response.
R弹就此投下了 我以为我们不用坚定这个词了
- There goes the R-bomb. - I thought we weren't doing robust.
我以为我们还在深思熟虑中
I thought we were still on considered.
我们有这个世界上最好的军队
We have the best military in the world.
而且我们无所畏惧
And we are not afraid.
嘿 Mike? 是的 女士
- Hey, Mike? - Yes, ma'am.
在华盛顿的屁股上贴上温度计
Stick a thermometer up Washington's ass.
看我创造了多少热度
See how much heat I just created.
正在掰臀瓣呢
Parting the cheeks.
你知道坚定是我的词 她偷了我的词
You know robust is my word. She stole my word.
她本该装傻的 Mike
She was supposed to be dull, Mike.
你在《政客》上有看到我的那张照片了吗?
And did you see that photo of me in Politico?
天哪 我看起来像便秘了一样
My God, I look constipated.
不 你没有 到我的办公室来见我
- No, you don't. - Meet me in my office.
你看起来不像便秘 而是相反的那种状况
You don't look constipated. You look the opposite of it.
便秘的反面是什么 Mike
What's the opposite of constipated, Mike?
放松的 不
Relieved. - No.
放松可不是便秘的反面 Mike
Relieved is not the opposite of constipated, Mike.
挂上电话 笨蛋
Hang up the phone, dummy.
嘿 女士 你看过这个了吗 这是什么
- Hey, ma'am, you seen this yet? - What is it?
就是《邮报》
Just the Post.
《副总统的姐妹坚定地推波助澜》?
VP sister act robusting the moves?
女士 还有...是的
Ma'am, there's also... yeah.
这他妈的都是什么
What in the living fuck is this?
今早《特区报纸》出的词汇云
It's a word cloud from this morning's DC Press.
每个词的大小都和它们被使用的总次数挂钩
The size of each word corresponds to its total number of uses.
人们难道不再使用句子了吗
Do people not use sentences anymore?
好吧 我是说 关于你的词 我是说 坚定占了主导地位
Well, I mean, your word... I mean, robust is dominating.
那么 你知道 这很好
So, you know, that's good.
看这个词 Sue
Look at the word Sue.
是的 Sue成功上榜 那边也有
- Sue made it. - Sure. It's there, too.
那么 Selina在哪
Well, where's the word Selina?
哦 它 唔...
Oh, it, um...
它 呃...
It's, uh...
我刚刚看到了
I just saw it.
哈! 那里 就在那
Ha! There. There it is.
看它有多微小
Look how teeny tiny that is.
它比崩溃大
It's bigger than collapse.
它那么微小是因为技术上你有四个名字
It's teeny tiny because technically you have four names.
副 总统 Selina Meyer
Vice President Selina Meyer.
哦 还有那些...我们不会谈论的昵称
Yeah, plus all the nicknames that we don't talk about.
我是说 而Sue只有一个名字 就像波卡洪塔斯(印第安公主)或者希特勒一样
I mean, Sue only has one name like Pocahontas or Hitler.
或者莫比(《白鲸记》)和大脚怪什么的 嘿 Sue
- Or Moby or Bigfoot. - Hey, Sue!
Sue! 是的 女士?
- Sue! - Yes, ma'am?
什么? 你他妈的不是Sue
What? You're not fucking Sue.
我是Cliff 我正在顶Sue的班
I'm Cliff. I'm filling in for Sue
她正为6号的二次听证做准备
while she preps for her return appearance on the sixth.
她要二次听证?
She has a return appearance?
她返场要做什么?
What does she need an encore for?
啊 那就是个返场表演 开始准备你的爆米花吧
Yeah, it's an encore. Start popping your popcorn.
好吧 非常感谢 非Sue不可电视台
- Okay, thank you very much. - Must Sue TV.
我说够了 谢谢
I said that's enough. Thank you.
Gary 我们需要开始准备
Gary, we need to start prepping
所有参议员的就职仪式了
for the whole senator swearing-in thing.
哦 是的 到了Gary-OK时间了 是的
- Oh, yeah. It's Gary-oke time. - Yes, it is.
好吧 我会为每个参议员准备一张卡片
All right, I put together one card for each senator.
事实上 女士 我对这儿的机会有些想法
Actually, ma'am, I had some ideas about some opportunities here.
我觉得如果我们能
I think it'd be a good idea if we focus more
更多的专注每个参议员各自的政策 而不是闲话家常的话会很好
on each senator's particular policy interests rather than small talk.
哦 我不认为那是个坏主意 什么?
- Yeah, I don't think that's a bad idea. - What?
是的 拿着外套 我觉得可行
Yeah, take the coat. That makes sense to me.
我想...哦 Sue在那
I think that... oh, there's Sue.
好的 离我远点 Sue!
Okay, get away from me. Sue!
Sue! 不 真的Sue
Sue! No, the real Sue.
离她的耳朵远点 听到了吗
You stay away from her ear. Do you hear me?
Gary-OK已经完了 我的朋友 现在是Danny-OK的时代了
Gary-oke is done, my friend. It's time for Danny-oke now.
Danny-OK? 一个时代的结束 哥们 一个时代的结束
- Danny-oke? - End of an era, buddy. End of an era.
别犯蠢了 我不出名
Don't be ridiculous. I'm not famous.
也许只在特区
Maybe only in DC.
哦 是的 我和Kim Kardashian (卡戴珊家族的风头人物)
Oh, yeah, me and Kim Kardashian.
哦 我得走了 再见 再见 再见 女士?
Oh, I've got to go. Bye, bye, bye. Ma'am?
你为什么不坐下来 Sue? 哦 抱歉 女士
- Why don't you take a seat, Sue? - Oh, sorry, ma'am.
坐下 Sue
Sit down, Sue.
好吧 我得跟你说说理...
All right, I've got a bone to pick...
女士 我知道你很喜欢我 但现在你会要恨我
Ma'am, I know you really love me, but now you're gonna hate me.
什么?
What?
国防部长Maddox刚和彭博通讯社做了访谈
Sec Def Maddox just did an interview with Bloomberg.
啊?
Yeah?
他现在的措辞是激进的回应
He's now calling for an aggressive response.
激进的? 是的 我也刚收到了
- - Aggressive? Yeah, I just got that, too.
激进把坚定给灭了?
Does aggressive trump robust?
这词更坚定
Well, it's robustier.
不 坚定就像石头 而激进像是布
No, robust is like a rock and aggressive is like paper.
糟了 布包石头啊 我忘了
Oh, shoot, paper covers rock. I forget about that.
刚收到Ben的短信 然后呢 他说什么
- We just got a text from Ben. - And? What's his word?
原话是:把-副-总-统-弄-这-儿-来 我-们-要-他-妈-开-会
His word is get-the-vice-president-over-here right-now-we're-having-a-fucking-meeting.
全用连字符连成了一个词
It's all one word hyphenated.
提醒我一下 你演讲怎么说的?
Remind me, you said what?
你的回应应该怎样? 坚定
your response needs to be What? - Robust.
坚定 然后你说? 激进
Robust. And you said? - Aggressive.
看到问题了吗 没有
- You see the problem? - No, I don't.
这俩是不同的词
They're different words.
不同的词意味着什么?
And saying different words means what?
意味着我们的...
It means we're not on the same...
减肥菜单不同? 意见不同
Diet? - Page.
我以为你要说减肥菜单呢 Ben
Oh, I thought you were gonna say diet, Ben.
我不喜欢你的腔调 而且这件事我也不用向你
- I don't like your tone. - And I don't have to answer to you, Ben.
或者是Lara Croft 汇报 Ben
Or to Lara Croft here for that matter.
也许不是 但我们都为总统工作
Yeah, perhaps not, but we all work for the president.
顺便问一下 伟大法力强大的Oz国巫师在哪儿啊
Oh, where is the great and powerful Oz, by the way?
听着 我们都知道如果白宫没有总统
Listen, we all know the White House would work so much better
会运转得更好 但是确实有
if there wasn't a president, but there is.
所以我们只能接受
So we work around that.
具体表现就是
And we do that by sticking
得使用同一个操蛋的词
to the same fucking words.
而你的工作就是协调此事 大师
And it's your job to coordinate that, maestro.
没错 所以从现在开始 那个词是有计划的回应
That's right. So from now on, the words are calculated response.
有计划 这个听起来很...
Calculated? That sounds so...
有计划 很娘 我打算这么说
- Calculated? - Pussy-ass, that's what I was gonna say.
你得在总统屁股底下点把火
You've got to light a fire under the president's butt.
赶紧来点实际行动吧
Let's get some action here.
她开了一次枪就以为自己是沙漠里的隆美尔元帅 (二战德军著名将领 绰号沙漠之狐)
She fires a gun one time and she thinks she's Rommel in the desert.
告诉你 我是个好枪手
Yeah, let me tell you something. I'm a good shot.
知道吗 我可能要开始 知道吗
You know what? I may even start... you know,
不管怎么说吧  携枪 这个如何
whatever it's called... packing heat. How about that?
你这么做的时候 就是我支持枪支管制的时候
When you do that, I'm gonna start supporting gun control.
我有面条的消息了 他在说什么
- I have news on the noodles. - What's he talking about?
人质的事我们可以行动了 面条好新闻啊
We Can move on The hostages. - Cock-a-noodle-doo.
天啊 我现在都想亲你了 但我永远不会这么做
Oh, my God. I'd kiss you right now, but I'm never gonna do that.
我们最快可以6号或者9号行动
Earliest we could go in would be the sixth or the ninth.
我们得早点 你知道总统大人的啦
We got to go early. You know POTUS.
如果我们给他充足的时间 他会改变主意的
If we give him enough time, he's gonna change his mind.
他会永远拖下去的
He's gonna procrasterbate forever.
副总统女士 哈? 在
Madam Vice President? - Huh? Yeah.
给我一秒钟
Um, just give me one second.
一秒钟
One second.
Amy 给办公室打电话
Amy, call the office.
副总统办公室 是副总统
Office of The Vice President. - this is The Vice President.
是的 不 不 我是副总统
- Yes, it is. - No, no, this is the vice president.
好吧 抱歉 女士 没事
- Oh, okay. I'm sorry, ma'am. - It's fine.
看看我的行事历 看看6号那天
Look into my calendar and tell me if there is anything
有没有不能推的事
on the sixth that is immovable.
没有 女士 看起来都可以推掉
Uh, no, ma'am, it all looks moveable.
唯一不能推的就是Sue在6号的二次听证会
The only thing that can't move is Sue's second hearing appearance on the sixth.
噢 那是6号? 是的 女士
- Oh, that's on the sixth? - Yes, ma'am.
设置你的硬盘录像机 我在想 好吧 你挂了
Set your DVR. I'm thinking of... okay, you hung up.
先生们 就是6号了
Well, gentlemen, the sixth it's gonna be.
咱们尽快把这些孩子送回家吧
Let's bring these kids home as soon as possible.
那就这么定了?
So we're all agreed?
6号对坏人来说将是糟糕的一天
The sixth, it's gonna be a bad day for the bad guys.
咱们去找总统大人吧
Let's go find POTUS.
你选6号是因为比9号早?
Now you went with the sixth because it's before the ninth?
当然 跟Sue回委员会听证这事没关系?
- Yeah, of course. - And Sue's return to the committee
你知道我对什么感兴趣吗
- has nothing to do with it? - You know what I'm interested in?
把无辜的美国人安全送回家
Getting innocent Americans home safe and sound, right?
把6号所有的事都给我推了
Move everything off of the sixth for me.
你可以把那天的日程清空了 好的 女士
- You can clear that. - Absolutely, ma'am.
唯一我需要推的就是参议员宣誓就职典礼
The only thing I need to move is the senator swearing-in ceremony,
所以没问题
so we're good.
什么
What?
参议员宣誓就职典礼
The senator swearing-in ceremony.
你说一切都可以推
You said that everything was moveable.
这不能推啊
And that's not moveable.
这不能推
That's immoveable.
当然没什么不能推的
Surely nothing is immoveable.
Amy 这就像对牛弹琴
Amy, this is like explaining gravity to a chicken.
参议员宣誓典礼是板上钉钉的事了
The senator swearing-in ceremony is set in stone.
她是参议院主席
She's the president of the Senate.
所有新当选的参议员宣誓就职都得她主持
She swears in all newly elected senators.
对吧 懂吗 明白吗
Right? You get that? You understand it?
你需要Google一下吗 不 女士 我懂
- Do you need to Google it? - No, ma'am, I understand.
我觉得你不懂
I don't think you do understand.
因为你在笑 你为什么笑
Because you are grinning. Why are you grinning?
我没笑 你在笑
- I'm not grinning. - You are grinning.
你惹了法国那么大的麻烦
You have made a fuckup the size of France
还有脸笑?
and you are fucking grinning about it.
我尽量不笑 我不知道我的脸为什么这种形状
I'm trying not to. I'm not sure why my face is doing this.
靠 好吧
- Oh, damn it. - Okay.
我不知道怎么回事
I don't know what's going on,
但她不是刚才那个意思
but she didn't mean what she just said, okay?
好吧 女士 还有什么事
Okay. Ma'am, is there anything...
机密 天啊
- Classified! - Oh, my God!
我力推的6号 对吧
I pushed for the sixth, right?
然后如愿以偿 那是我的大日子啊 Amy
I got my date. This is my date, Amy.
那是我的人质拯救任务
This is my hostage rescue mission.
那天最重要的事
The most important thing on the day
就是不能在行为举止上露出疑点
is we can't look suspicious in our movements.
我知道 我知道怎么表现正常
Yeah, I know that. I know how to act normal, okay?
我会正常的 会成功的
I'll be normal. It's gonna be great.
真不敢相信我现在的处境
I can't believe I'm in this position.
都是Cliff的错 那个他娘的傻笑Evok [星球大战物种]
This is all Cliff's fault, that grinning fucking Ewok.
他们都在战况室
They're all in the situation room.
我却困在这儿给一大堆参议员宣誓
I'm stuck here swearing in a shitload of senators.
虚拟战况室就在后边
Well, the virtual sit room is right back there
我们在那有战况室的安全远程视频
and we've got a secure video teleconference
所以... 噢 太好了
- in the situation room, so... - Oh, great.
我和历史的安全远程视频
My secure video teleconference with history.
好的 女士 你还得宣誓33个参议员呢
Okay, ma'am, you got 33 senators to get through.
天啊 我感觉像是一天要干200个男人的AV女优
Oh, boy. Well, I feel like that porn star who had to do 200 men in one day.
至少她还能躺着 对吧
At least she got to lie down, right?
让这个可爱的家庭进来
Well, let's bring this beautiful family in.
看看这个 你们都有很好的血统
Oh, look at this. You all have good blood.
怎么了 我能看出来 就在这儿
What's up? I can see it. It's right here.
这又不是总统的事 为什么拖油瓶在这儿
This isn't a POTUS thing. Why is scrotus here?
就当我是啦啦队的呗 Mike
Think of me as a cheerleader, Mike.
天啊 脑海中出现了
Oh, God. I'm imagining you
你躺在铺满玫瑰花瓣浴缸里的画面
in a bathtub full of rose petals.
谢谢 可以走了 Brian 该你了
Thank you. Off you go. Brian, you're up.
来 来 副总统女士
- Come, come. - Madam Vice President.
恭喜 荣幸之至
Congratulations. - What an honor.
很高兴见到你
It's so good to see you.
我想知道你的电影拍得怎么样了
I want to know how all your filmmaking is going.
什么 等等
Beg pardon? - And So on.
什么 钓鱼
Beg pardon? - your fishing.
是的 很好 我还在等着钓那条大鱼
Oh, yeah. It's good. I'm still hunting for that big one.
那是我们大家的目标 我们都想要大鱼 对吧
Well, that's all we want. We all want the big one, don't we?
她刚刚是影射我了吗 是的 是的
Did She just make an innuendo? - Yep. Yep.
我坚持真理
That I will bear true faith...
与忠诚 我自愿承担这一义务
and allegiance to the same. That I take this obligation
毫无保留 决不逃避
freely without any mental reservation or purpose of evasion
而我将忠实履行
and that I will well and faithfully discharge
我的职责 所以 Brian保佑我
the duties of the office of which I am about to enter, so help me Brian.
是的 我是Brian
- Yes. - Uh, I am Brian.
我知道 我以为你要说 上帝保佑
- I know. - I think you mean, So help you God.
是的 是的 上帝保佑你
Yes, yes. Oh, so help you God.
上帝保佑我 保佑我 是的
- So help me God. - Me, God, yes.
天啊 好吧 让家人都进来吧
Oh, my God. Okay, let's get the family in here.
怎么回事
What's going on?
只会是一时的问题 她会没事的
It's just a blip. She's gonna be fine.
我是Ruby 噢 Ruby
- I'm Ruby. - Oh, Ruby.
我希望那是我堂兄妹的名字
Oh, I wish that was my cousin's name.
这是我听过的最差的寒暄了
This is the worst small talk I've ever heard.
而且我把自己说过的也包括在内 而我的很糟糕
And I'm including mine in that and mine is horrible.
她说过更糟的
She's done worse.
想不起来什么时候 但她有过
I can't think of when, but she has.
到你了 Maryanne 我的...
And off you go. Maryanne.
苍天上帝
What in the living...
老天爷啊 你怎么会在这儿
Lord of Christ are you doing here?
但你在 我在
- But you are. - I'm here.
所以你新年过得不错喽
So you had a good New Year's?
是的 我们在Vermont滑雪
Yes, we were skiing in Vermont.
世事无常啊
Well, that's how the cookie crumbles.
咱们拍张照吧
Yeah, now let's take a photo.
西翼 我是Jonah
West Wing. Jonah.
好吧 Philip Dorsey是最后一个 所以他会很快
Okay, Philip Dorsey's the last one, so he's gonna be quick.
他老婆刚死 他没有家人了
His wife just died and he has no family left.
太好了 对我们来讲
That's great. For us, I mean.
因为我们完事了 好吧
- 'Cause we're done. - Okay.
Amy 到点了
Amy, it's time o'clock.
什么是到点了 到点了
- What's time o'clock? - Time o'clock.
这个 我真的受不了了
This is... I can't take this anymore.
何不代我向Patty问好?
And so won't you give my love to Patty?
她去世了 是的 是的
She passed away. - Yes. Yes.
抱歉 女士 到点了
Excuse me, ma'am. It is time o'clock.
好吧 我们宣誓吧 Philip
All right, let's get swearing, Philip.
我庄严宣誓
I do solemnly swear...
我会我会支持和维护
that I will support and defend
美国宪法
the Constitution of the United States
反对国内外一切敌对势力
against all enemies, foreign and domestic.
我坚持真理
That I will bear true faith...
也许她又怀孕了呢 天啊
- Maybe she's pregnant again. - Oh, God.
或者她在更年期
Or she's menopausal.
天啊 她会想要睾丸激素的 我得离开这儿
Oh, God, she's gonna want that testosterone gel. I'm out of here.
上帝保佑我 上帝保佑我
- ...so help me God. - ...so help me God.
上帝保佑我
So help me God.
我得走了 Philip
Uh, I have to move on, Philip.
他们最终都离开了我
They all leave me eventually.
出事了 出事了 怎么了
Something's up. Something's up. What's going on?
女士 女士 这儿 好吧
- Ma'am. Ma'am. Right here. - Oh, yeah.
女士 我得 不 这儿不需要你了 Gary
- Ma'am, I've got... - No, you're not needed here, Gary.
这是男人的活 女士 我可以
- This is man's work. - Ma'am, should I...
你也该走了 Dan 不
Same goes for you, Dan. No.
让我们嗨上天吧 抱歉 伙计们
- Let's black out till we drop. - Sorry, fellas.
我现在要关门了
I'll just be closing this door right now.
等一下 Jonah进去了吗
Wait a minute. Jonah's going in?
向历史打招呼吧 女士 天啊
- Say hi to history, ma'am. - Oh, God.
他们占领战况室我的是战况屎?
The men get the situation room, I get the shituation room?
女士 通信现在应该是通的 噢
- Ma'am, the comms should be live now. - Oh.
先生们
Hi, gentlemen.
希望你们听到了刚才的笑话
I hope you heard that joke.
那是特意说给你们听的
That was meant for you to hear it.
副总统女士 这位是Mercer将军
Madam Vice President, this is General Mercer.
太棒了 跟你打赌三号机会拍到杀人镜头
This is so awesome. I'll bet you camera three gets a kill.
将军 总统先生
General, Mr. President.
好牧人行动进行顺利 女士
Operation Good Shepherd is proceeding well, ma'am.
我们现在看的是黑鹰直播
We are looking at live feeds from cams
我们要进去了
aboard the Black Hawks and we are about to go in.
祝你们好运 先生们 女士
- Good luck, gentlemen. - Ma'am.
开枪的时候会很响 副总统女士
When the guns go off, they will be loud, Madam Vice President,
所以不要爆粗口
so no swearing.
George 你这话
George, comments like that
极度不合时宜
are incredibly inappropriate
在有人命悬一线的时候说
when people's lives are at stake.
我得再来一杯
I've got to get a refill here.
老式喷气飞机需要加油了 打扰一下
Old jumbo needs a refill. Excuse me.
拍得不错 女士 Jonah 现在世界上
- It's a good photo, ma'am. - Jonah, there are more important things
有更重要的事
going on in the world right now.
嗯 不错
Oh, yeah. Huh.
战报确认
Acquisition is confirmed.
鸡蛋回篮子里了
The eggs are back in the basket!
好的 鸡蛋蛋
Yeah! Eggs-shak-a-laka!
就爆在你面前 鸡蛋
In your fucking face, eggs.
什么 人质 救出来了?
What? The hostages? We got 'em?
是的
Yeah!
历史丰碑啊...
Legacy marker. Yeah!
Gary. Gary.
Sue回去听证的事就上不了新闻了
So Sue's return to the hearing's wiped off the news map.
这是今天人们最不关注的事了 拜托
That's the last thing on anyone's mind today. Come on.
当然 当然
Of course. Of course.
去年办公用品的花费
Last year's expenditure on office supplies
与前一年的持平
was held at the exact same level as the previous year.
也就是总合...
Which means that the total sum...
看起来你已经是过去时了 Wilson小姐
Seems like you're no longer news, Miss Wilson.
你的15分钟结束了
Your 15 minutes might be up.
尘归尘
Ashes to ashes,
坚定归土
robust to dust.
嘿 Sue 续集怎么样
Oh, hey, Sue. How was the sequel?
短
Short.
被名誉这头怪兽无情地榨干后抛弃了
Pumped and dumped by the fame monster, huh?
我从国家安全委员会拿到了全面的任务评估报告
Oh, I got the full mission eval from the NSC.
咱们跟副总统谈谈吧 走
- Let's speak to the veep. - Let's go.
怎么了
Yep?
女士 恭喜 女士
- Ma'am. - Congratulations, ma'am.
谢谢 Ryan先生
Thank you, Mr. Ryan.
好牧人行动是个巨大的胜利
Operation Good Shepherd... total success.
当然 永远忠钱
Yeah! Semper fucking fee.
忠诚 忠诚 忠诚对
- Fi. - Fi. Fi, right.
所有人质都完好无损地被救出
All hostages recovered unharmed.
只有一名受伤 有详细情况吗
Only one injury. - Detail on that injury?
一个海军陆战队员 第二侦察营
A Marine sergeant, 2nd recon battalion,
流弹 他失去了一只腿
stray ordnance, he lost a leg.
等等 等等
Uh... wait, wait.
你是说我们有一个海军陆战队失去了一只腿?
You mean one of our Marines lost a leg?
是的 女士 他的左腿 女士
Yes, ma'am. His left leg, ma'am.
Um...
整条腿?
the entire leg?
我相信他的腿从膝盖之上都没有了
I believe he lost from above the knee.
所以他们可以...
Oh, so they were able to...
医治他的脚就行了?
just salvage his foot?
不 我认为他...
No, I believe he lost from above...
从膝盖之上往下基本没有腿了
he basically doesn't have a leg from above the knee down.
他是行动中的一员吗
Was he part of the operation?
是的 他本来应该8号轮岗的
Yes. He was actually due to be rotated out on the eighth.
8号
Oh, on the eighth.
好吧
Huh. Okay.
他
Is he...
他很疼吗
ahem, is he in a lot of pain?
不 女士 噢 很好
- Oh, no, ma'am. - Oh, good.
不 他现在在医学昏迷中
No, he's in an induced coma.
但我想他醒过来的时候...
But I suppose when he wakes up...
我需要点新鲜空气 抱歉
I just need to get some air. Excuse me.
再次恭喜 女士 千万次地感谢
- Congratulations again, ma'am. - Thanks a million.
恭喜 女士 谢谢
- Congratulations, ma'am. - Thank you.
我让一个士兵丢了一只腿 Mike 很好 很好
- I lost a man his leg, Mike. - So good. So good.
不 不 不 我让一个人失去了腿 Mike
No, no, no. I lost a man his leg, Mike.
谢谢 谢谢 伙计们
Thanks. Thanks, guys.
谢谢
Thank you.
女士 我只是想说表现太完美了
Ma'am, I just want to say consummate performance.
不止拯救了人质
Not only did you rescue the hostages,
而且全歼了Sue
but you annihilated Sue.
你选了她听证那天来行动
You picked the operation date to blow her appearance off the map.
我是说 天才啊 女士 天才啊
I mean, genius play, ma'am. Genius.
我称之为暗中出击
I call that overshadowboxing.
知道吗 Dan
You know what, Dan?
你一直离一个人耳边这么近的叨叨
The problem with being so close to somebody's ear all the time
你会开始觉得你能读懂他们的心思
is that you begin to think that you can see inside their head,
但你不能 Dan 你不能
but you can't, Dan. You can't.
明白吗 明白 女士
- Do you understand that? - Understood, ma'am.
嘿 女士 是的
- Hey, ma'am. - Yes?
给你来杯肉桂咖啡什么的
Can I get you a cinnamon mocha or something?
好吧 我给你拿
Yeah, let me get that for you.
一个时代结束了 哥们
End of an era, buddy.
一个时代结束了
End of an era.
我害一个人失去了一条腿
I lost a man his leg.
不要再说了 女士
Please stop saying that, ma'am.
他会重新站起来的 我有感觉
He'll bounce back. I got a feeling.
女士 副总统有时得
Ma'am, the vice president sometimes has to do
做坏事才能得来好结果
bad things to make good things happen.
这条腿只是你所付出的代价
The leg is just the price of admission
为了达到现在这个位置
to the place you wanted to be.
也许我们可以邀请他去白宫
Well, maybe we could invite him to the White House.
知道吗 一旦他重新站...
You know, once he's back up on his...
当然 我们会把他推上坡道的
Sure, we'll roll out the ramps.
女士 这年头他们用的义肢
Ma'am, some of the prosthetic legs they have these days
有的和真腿一样好
are as good as real legs.
我向你保证他们比我的烂腿好
I guarantee you they're better than my shitty legs.
我讨厌我的腿 事实上 如果我有选择
I hate my legs. In fact, if I had the choice...
Huh?
无所谓 我要走了
Never mind. I'm gonna go.
嘿 女士 想来点
Hey, ma'am. How would you like
杏仁小面包吗
a nice little almond croissant?
当然 太好了
Oh, yeah. I would love that.
好的 好的
Okay. Okay.
能弄大点吗
Can you make it a big one
所以你可以把我塞面包里
so you can stuff me inside of it
然后把我偷运出去吗
and smuggle me out of here?
当然
Of course I can.
里面可能还会有覆盆子惊喜噢
And there might be a little raspberry surprise in them.
好吧 谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
我的荣幸
My pleasure.